Christopher James King

Columbus, OH - chrisking610@gmail.com - 419-936-4045 - dacking15.github.io/Personal-Website/

DESCRIPTION

I am currently working remotely as the lead developer for a nonprofit named Equality Lab. My dream is to work as a gameplay programmer at a major game development studio, but would be happy to gain some experience working in a team of software developers.

EDUCATION

The Ohio State University, Columbus, OH

BS in Computer Science and Engineering, 2020 Specialized in Computer Graphics and Game Design Media Marketing and Communications Scholars, Pi Kappa Phi Fraternity

EMPLOYMENT

Equality Lab, Miami, Florida, June 2020 - Present, Remote

At Equality Lab, I work with a team of developers and designers from around the world to develop virtual reality experiences for USIP, Pôle emploi, and Miami Dade County Schools. As the lead developer, I have done a variety of work from setting up Hubs Cloud servers with AWS to integrating game physics into the platform.

Classroom and Digital Union Tech Support, Columbus, Ohio, January 2020 – March 2020 Sidon Lebanese Bakery and Grill, Toledo, Ohio, May 2019 – January 2020

PROJECTS: Available on my Portfolio Website

Tanks 3D, May 2020 – June 2020

Independent, Unity, C#, Procedural Generation, Multiplayer, Windows 10, Web GL, Xbox.

Save the Children Presents Eyes of Mariam, January 2020 – May 2020

Collaborative, Animation Capstone, VR, Oculus Quest, Unity, C#, Windows 10, Mixamo, Xbox. *Our project was chosen by Equality Lab, our Animation Capstone sponsor, to be placed on their website and developed further for Save the Children.*

COVID 19 Interactive Mirror, January 2020 – May 2020

Collaborative, Data Visualization, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, D3, Excel, GitHub, Python.